{
    "subject": "resource/Maria_Schell",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Austria",
    "human_readable": "Maria Schell died in Austria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8928340673446655,
            "question": "Is there any information about Maria Schell's life before her death in Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8888394236564636,
            "question": "Was Maria Schell Austrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8368707299232483,
            "question": "Where did Maria Schell die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.680611789226532,
            "question": "What year did Maria Schell die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6353849172592163,
            "question": "What was the cause of Maria Schell's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5663670897483826,
            "question": "Are there any memorials or tributes to Maria Schell in Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2432071566581726,
            "question": "What was Maria Schell's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23183175921440125,
            "question": "Were there any famous people associated with Maria Schell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18855392932891846,
            "question": "Was Maria Schell known for any particular roles or films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1627732366323471,
            "question": "Did Maria Schell have any family members who were also in the entertainment industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maria Schell died in Austria.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2821_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Maria Schell known for any particular roles or films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2821_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any famous people associated with Maria Schell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2821_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Maria Schell's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2821_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2821_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, Maria Schell died of pneumonia on April 26, 2005, in Preitenegg, Carinthia, Austria. This information supports the triple that she died in Austria."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Maria Schell died on April 26, 2005, in Preitenegg, Austria. This supports the statement that Maria Schell died in Austria."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}